

# **Daniel Blacha** Java Developer

#### About me

For over 4 years I have been working as a Java Backend Developer at Pentacomp, creating an e-health platform in Java and Spring technologies. At work, I value new technologies and the SCRUM framework. I prefer remote work.

City	Warszawa
Phone	+48 791 204 880
Email	daniel.blacha@gmail.com
Assets	Open to new challenges, punctual, reliable,hard working, easygoing
Languages	Polish 🗹 🗹 🗹 🖸 🗆
Interests	➤ Motorcycles

## **Experience**

### Pentacomp

10.2017 - currently

Backend Java Developer

Working with technologies: Spring, Spring Boot, REST, SOAP, MySQL, MongoDb, Maven

Configuring and automating CI, CD processes in Jenkins and

Writing unit and integration tests based on TestNG, JUnit, Mockito

Creating technical documentation of the project Software development using the SCRUM framework

**Ait Solutions** 5.2017 - 10.2017

Junior Java Web Developer

1.2017 - 3.2017 Deloitte

Junior business consultant (Core Banking System)

Akademia Kodu 2.2017 - 11.2017

Training begginer programmers in BootCamp

### **Courses & Certificates**

Professional Scrum Product Owner I	12.2021
Professional Scrum Master I	9.2021
Spring Certified Professional	2.2021
Oracle Certified Professional Java Programmer	2.2020
Oracle Certified Associate Java Programmer	6.2018
Java BootCamp	11.2016
Project Management	6.2016

### **Education**

The School of Banking and Management in Cracow	2015 - 2016
Warsaw University of Technology	2008 - 2013

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.